[{"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Infinix"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.7\"", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u2248108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "no", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,Turkish,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.6", "Display Resolution": "2408x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP,2MP,5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G"}, "Other": {"Phone model": "Samsung Galaxy A13 4G A135U", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Samsung Model": "Samsung Galaxy A13", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "KR(Origin)", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "VIVO"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "7.0", "Display Resolution": "3200*1440", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "65W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ax,802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 8 Gen 1", "vivo Model": "X Note", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2712*1220", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "200MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "120W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "no"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "no", "Other Features": "EIS stabilization,Optical Stabilization,5G Mobile Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi Note 13 Pro+", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "\u22644.0\"", "Display Resolution": "176 x 220 pixels", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "No", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "1.3MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "None Front Camera"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1000", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Others"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "2G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "no"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "no", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black/Silver", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11b/g", "Samsung Model": "S3600", "Design": "Flip", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "Polish,German,French,Norwegian,Turkish,ITALIAN,Spanish,Portuguese,Russian,English,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "DOOGEE"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.5", "Display Resolution": "1170x480", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Doogee Model": "Smini"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Huawei"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "huawei"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.5", "Display Resolution": "1920x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3340", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "GSM,WCDMA,LTE", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "4.1"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"4G": "FDD LTE 1800/2100", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Standby Time": "Up To 150 Hours", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz", "Main Rear Camera Sensor": "SONY IMX386", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Huawei Model": "HiSilicon Kirin 655", "Optical Zoom": "2X", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "Display size range": "Large (6.5-7\")", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES", "CPU Core Quantity": "Octa Core"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "20MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 3.0", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization"}, "Other": {"RAM+ROM": "12GB+256GB", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi K40S", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "LG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.7", "Display Resolution": "2560x1440", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3200mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 3.0", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Screen": "1 screen(not dual screen)", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "LG Model": "V20", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 820"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "realme"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.7", "Display Resolution": "1080x2412", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Curved Screen,Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "Other", "Front Camera Pixel": "Other"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "FlashCharge", "Charging Power": "100W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "Other", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"rear camera": "50 MP Sony IMX766 OIS main camera", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "realme model": "GT2 Master Explorer Edition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,French,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "realme"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.7", "Display Resolution": "2412*1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Curved Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "200MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "realme SuperDart", "Charging Power": "100W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "5 G,3G,2G,4G", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Fast Charging Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition,Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,EAC", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Turkish,Norwegian,Polish,Arabic,Korean,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Japanese", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BlackBerry"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "2.46", "Display Resolution": "240x320", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "No", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "NONE"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "2MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "None Front Camera"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1150", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Other Smartphone OS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "2G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "no", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "White/Black", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11b/g", "Blackberry Model": "8520", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Norwegian", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "DOOGEE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.43 inch", "Display Resolution": "2400 x 1080 pixels", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "8MP,24MP,\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "6000mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,RoHS", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Doogee Model": "DOOGEE V20 Pro"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.53inch", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"ROM": "Global ROM", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.0", "Display Resolution": "854x480", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5200", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Item Condition": "New", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "Flip", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Origin": "Mainland China"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OPPO"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.7", "Display Resolution": "720x1440", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2900", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "MTK Model": "Helio P23 MT6763T", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "OPPO Model": "A83", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "DOOGEE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.5 inch", "Display Resolution": "2400 x 1080 pixels", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10000mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card,1 SIM Card+1 eSIM"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Brand Name": "BLACKVIEW", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Doogee Model": "BV8900"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OUKITEL"}, "Storage": {"ROM": "64G"}, "Memory": {"RAM": "4GB"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.5", "Display Resolution": "1440x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "1.3MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"FDD": "B1/B3/B7/B8/B19/B20", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UMIDIGI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.53inch", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5150", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ax", "Design": "BAR", "": "295369929", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G25", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.528", "Display Resolution": "720*1600", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10600", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Display": "6.528-Inch In-Cell Punch-Hole Display, 720*1600", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,RoHS,WEEE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "nomu"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.2", "Display Resolution": "1280x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "21MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "21MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Play Store": "YES", "Biometrics Technology": "Rear-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "MTK Model": "MT6750T", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.52\"", "Display Resolution": "720*1600", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "20MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Android version": "Android 12", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "LG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "3.2", "Display Resolution": "320x480", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "3MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "Other"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1500", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black/White/Green/Pink", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g", "Design": "Flip", "LG Model": "D486", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Nokia"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "1.8", "Display Resolution": "128x160", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "No", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "NONE"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u22641MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "None Front Camera"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1020", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Other", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Dumbphone OS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "2G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "no"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "no", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "FI(Origin)", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67\"", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "OLED", "Screen Type": "Flexible Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "200MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "120W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi Note 12 Pro+ plus", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Motorola"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.62", "Display Resolution": "1080 x 2400", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Super AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "FlashCharge", "Charging Power": "65W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition,Rear-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58\u201d", "Display Resolution": "1080*2408 FHD+", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "9600mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OPPO"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Storage": {"ROM": "256G"}, "Memory": {"RAM": "8G"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.53inch", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3765", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition", "Unlock Phones": "Yes", "Standby Time": "Other", "Design": "BAR", "Touch Screen Type": "Capacitive Screen", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Optical Zoom": "no", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,French,Korean,Japanese", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 710", "OPPO Model": "X", "CPU Core Quantity": "Octa Core", "Phone Type": "Smart Phones"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Huawei"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "huawei"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "7.7", "Display Resolution": "2248x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "OLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5065", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "66W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "HarmonyOS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Game Phone,Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"4G": "FDD LTE: B1/B2/B3/B4/B5/B7/B8/B12/B17/B18/B19/B20/B26/B28", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ax,802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES", "Huawei Model": "Mate X5"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.7", "Display Resolution": "1334*750", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "7MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2200", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "20W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Other": {"Item Condition": "Used", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Apple Model": "iPhone SE2022", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Origin": "Mainland China"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UNIWA"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.3", "Display Resolution": "1080*2340px", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "24MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "HD (720p) 120 fps,FullHD (1080p) 120 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.52 inch", "Display Resolution": "720x1600", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "6320mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 3.0", "Charging Power": "120W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi Note 11 Pro+", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.0", "Display Resolution": "1080x540(1080x540", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Other", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"telefony smartfony": "portable", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio P90", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.46", "Display Resolution": "1440x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Mini USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"condition": "used", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi 6", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MEIZU"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.2", "Display Resolution": "1080 x 2232", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "20MP,48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "20MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3600", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "GSM,WCDMA,LTE", "NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 855", "Meizu Model": "16S", "CPU Core Quantity": "Octa Core"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BlackBerry"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "3.5", "Display Resolution": "720x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "8MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "25", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Other Smartphone OS"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Blackberry Model": "Q20(CLASSIC)", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UMIDIGI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.5", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "24MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "61", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "": "BISON 2 /BISON 2 PRO", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.6", "Display Resolution": "2048x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"A136U": "Support 5G", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Samsung Model": "A13", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "LG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.5", "Display Resolution": "2560x1440", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3000", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 3.0", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"SIM Card Quantity": "Single SIM Card", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "LG Model": "G4", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "German,Polish,French,Norwegian,Turkish,ITALIAN,Spanish,Portuguese,Russian,English", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 808"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UMIDIGI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.53inch", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "20MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "6150", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Battery Capacity Range": "6000-7499mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio P60", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.52 inch", "Display Resolution": "1600 x 720 pixels", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4400mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,RoHS", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.6", "Display Resolution": "1480x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "13000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Samsung Model": "Samsung Galaxy J6 J600F", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OnePlus"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.41", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3700", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "20W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "GSM,CDMA,WCDMA,LTE", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "5.0"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Standby Time": "Other", "Main Rear Camera Sensor": "SONY IMX519", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Optical Zoom": "no", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Oneplus Model": "6T", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Display size range": "Middle (6-6.49\")", "Language": "Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 845", "Built in radiator": "no", "CPU Core Quantity": "Octa Core"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OPPO"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.8", "Display Resolution": "2520x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Folded Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u224832MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4300", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "44W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,French,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Infinix"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58\"", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Chipset": "Mediatek MT6833P Dimensity 810 (6 nm)", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,Turkish,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BlackBerry"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "2.8", "Display Resolution": "640x480", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "No", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "NONE"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "None Front Camera"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1230", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Other", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Other Smartphone OS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g", "Blackberry Model": "9930", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "German,Polish,French,Norwegian,ITALIAN,Spanish,Portuguese,Russian,English,Other", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u2248108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4820", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Storage": "6GB 64GB/ 6GB 128GB", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "redmi", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "HTC"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Storage": {"ROM": "32G"}, "Memory": {"RAM": "3G"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.0", "Display Resolution": "1920x1080", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "20MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "Other"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2840mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "GSM/WCDMA/LTE", "NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Front Camera Pixel": "4MP", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Unlock Phones": "Yes", "Standby Time": "Up To 48 Hours", "HTC Model": "ONE M9", "Design": "BAR", "Touch Screen Type": "Capacitive Screen", "Optical Zoom": "no", "Thickness": "Ultra Slim(<9mm)", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "Release Date": "2015", "Language": "French,German,Russian,Polish,English,Turkish,Norwegian,ITALIAN,Spanish,Portuguese", "CPU Core Quantity": "Octa Core", "Phone Type": "Smart Phones"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SOYES"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.55", "Display Resolution": "1280X640", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2100", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BLACKVIEW"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.6", "Display Resolution": "2408x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "MTK Model": "Helio G96", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ZTE"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.8", "Display Resolution": "FHD+ 1080x2400", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "2MP,8MP,\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500mah", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "65W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "ZTE Model": "redmagic 7"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BLACKVIEW"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.7''", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "15080", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "LG"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.2", "Display Resolution": "1920x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "13000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Phone model": "LG G2 D802", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "LG Model": "G2 32G", "Origin": "KR(Origin)", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.0", "Display Resolution": "1920x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "<2800", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Camo Green/Ruby Red/Titanium Grey", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Samsung Model": "G870A", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "Polish,German,French,Norwegian,Turkish,ITALIAN,Spanish,Portuguese,Russian,English,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 801", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OnePlus"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "3200x1440", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Curved Screen,Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "SuperVOOC", "Charging Power": "65W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Bluetooth": "Bluetooth 5.2", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Oneplus Model": "oneplus 9", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 888"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Redmi"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Storage": {"ROM": "128G"}, "Memory": {"RAM": "4GB"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.3", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "13MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "GSM,WCDMA,LTE", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "5.0"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Rear-mounted", "Standby Time": "Other", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "Flip", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Display size range": "Middle (6-6.49\")", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 660", "CPU Core Quantity": "Octa Core"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BlackBerry"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "2.46", "Display Resolution": "240x320", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "No", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "NONE"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "2MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "None Front Camera"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1150", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Other Smartphone OS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Blackberry Model": "9300", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11b/g", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,French,Spanish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Norwegian", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MIUI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Charge Turbo", "Charging Power": "67W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Charging": "67W turbo charging", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Note 12 Pro", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BLACKVIEW"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.1", "Display Resolution": "1560x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5180", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Blackview Model": "BV5200Pro", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}]